MAHABUB TAMIM

Content Creator



01744-463419

01734-845909 (Parants)

Palashbari, Gaibandha

Talertak, khilkhet, Dhaka (present)

itstamim.ban@gmail.com

1≡ 8712751521 (NID NO)

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Content Creator, with more than 5 years of experience in the creative industry. I have received various awards. national and international. I have gained a lot of experience in my work as a Content Creator. I have worked on several large projects in the past year.

Helping clients to solve their problems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

VIDEO EDITOR(REMOTE)

2020-2021

Edit Crew

This work was the first work of my life. Very good experience working with them. Worked on various projects for 1 year.My job in this company was to arrange footage and color grading. Which I liked very much.

CONTENT DIRECTOR

MohaKhadok (Food Brand Promoter) 2021-2022

This journey was amazing. I used to make content about different traditional foods. Our aim was to distribute Bangladeshi food to everyone. I used to care about how to make a content so that people can learn a lot by watching it.

ANDROID DEVELOPER

IT PLanet BD 2020-2023

I love working with apps. So I work as an apps developer in this company. Here I used to build an app from scratch

EDUCATION

Cantonment Public School & College Rangpur

Science GPA-5.00 HSC

BSC in Computer Science

Running Green University

PERSONAL SKILLS



Editing



Content Making



Speaking



Thinking



